Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5519
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
1945-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5519
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This is a collection of arbitration awards.
5658986
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 17, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 15, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (1914-1996) was a government official who specialized in labor arbitration and non-discrimination contracts, and wrote extensively on labor law and negotiations. He graduated from Temple University in 1937 and received a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania Law School in 1941. During the 1940s he was an attorney with the U.S. War Department, the National War Labor Board and the National Wage Stabilization Board. In 1948 he went to graduate school at Cornell University, from which he earned his Ph.D. in industrial and labor relations in 1951. In 1951 he joined the staff of the President's Committee on Government Contract Compliance. The Committee was abolished by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in August 1953 by Executive Order 10479 and was succeeded by the President's Committee on Government Contracts. Seidenberg was appointed Executive Director of the new committee and served until January 1960 when he resigned to become a full-time labor arbitrator. The Committee was responsible for enforcing non-discrimination clauses in government contracts, worked with private businesses to help them overcome job discrimination, and developed educational programs against ethnic and racial discrimination. The chairman was Vice President Richard Nixon, and the vice chairman was Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. In later years Seidenberg served on a number of boards of inquiry involving labor disputes. From 1970 to 1975 he was chairman of the Federal Services Impasses Panel which settled deadlocks in federal labor negotiations.
Scope and Contents
Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (1914-1996) was a government official who specialized in labor arbitration and non-discrimination contracts, and wrote extensively on labor law and negotiations. He graduated from Temple University in 1937 and received a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania Law School in 1941. During the 1940s he was an attorney with the U.S. War Department, the National War Labor Board and the National Wage Stabilization Board. In 1948 he went to graduate school at Cornell University, from which he earned his Ph.D. in industrial and labor relations in 1951. In 1951 he joined the staff of the President's Committee on Government Contract Compliance. The Committee was abolished by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in August 1953 by Executive Order 10479 and was succeeded by the President's Committee on Government Contracts. Seidenberg was appointed Executive Director of the new committee and served until January 1960 when he resigned to become a full-time labor arbitrator. The Committee was responsible for enforcing non-discrimination clauses in government contracts, worked with private businesses to help them overcome job discrimination, and developed educational programs against ethnic and racial discrimination. The chairman was Vice President Richard Nixon, and the vice chairman was Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. In later years Seidenberg served on a number of boards of inquiry involving labor disputes. From 1970 to 1975 he was chairman of the Federal Services Impasses Panel which settled deadlocks in federal labor negotiations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5007: U.S. Emergency Board No. 175 Transcripts and Exhibits 5027: U.S. Emergency Board No. 178 Transcripts 5031 A&B: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5229: Jacob Seidenberg Additional records 5468: Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration files
Arbitration, Industrial; Seidenberg, Jacob
5658986
- Special Board of Adjustment, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Special Adjustment Board, 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- SUNA -9-W, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 20-W, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 21-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 22-W, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 23-W, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 24-W, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 25-W, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 26-W, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 27-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 28-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 29-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 30-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 31-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 32-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 33-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 34-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 35-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 36-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 37-W, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- SBA #455 Case 1+2, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- SBA #455 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- SBA #455, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Award SBA #455, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- SBA #455 No. 32, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- SBA #455 Case No. 30, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Personal 16 P.L. Bol 507, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Award No. 69-LE S.D. E-13 61, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Award No. 70 L-E S.P. E. 1363, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Award No. 71-LE, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Award No. 72 - LE S.D. E-1370, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Award No. 73-LE, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Award No. 74-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Award NO. 75 L-E, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Award No. 76-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Award No. 77-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Award No. 78-LE, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Award No. 79-LE, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Award No. 80-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Award No. 81-LE, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Award NO. 82-LE, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Award No. 83-LE, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Award No. 84-LE, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Award No. 85-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Award No. 86-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Award No. 87-LE, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Award No. 47 P.L. Board No. 326, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Award No. 48, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Award No. 49-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Award No. 50, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Award No. 51, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Award No. 52, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Award NO. 53, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Award No. 54, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Award No. 55 - Lines East, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Award No. 56, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Award No. 57, 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Award 58 - S.D., 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Award No. 59 L-E, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Award No. 60, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Award No. 61, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Award No. 62, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Award NO. 63 -LE, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Award No. 64 -LE, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Award No. 65 -L-E, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Award No. 67 -LE, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Award No. 1, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Award No. 2, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Award No. 3, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Award No. 4 Case No. 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Award No. 5 Case No. 6, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Award No. 7 Case No. 9 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Case No. 10 Award No 8, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Award No. 9, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Award No. 10 Case No. 12, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Award No. 11 Case No. 13, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Award No. 13 Case No. 16, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Award No. 12 Case No. 14, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Award No. 14 Case No. 17, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Awards 15-16 Case Nos. 18-19, 1934-1969 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Award No. 17 Case No. 20, 1953-1967 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Award No. 18 Case No. 21, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Award No. 19 Case No. 22, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Award No. 20 Case No. 23, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Award No. 6 + Award No. 24 Case No. 8, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Award No. 95 -LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Award No. 96 -LE- S.D. 1430, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Award NO. 97 LE - S.R. 1434, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Award No. 98 -LE S.D. 1435, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Award No. 99 -L-E S.D. 1437, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Award No. 100 L-E S.D. 1438, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Award No. 101 S.D. 1289, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Award No. 102-LE, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Award No. 103 -LE S.D. 1131, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Award No. 104 L-E S.D. 1315, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Award No. 105 L-E S.D. 1369, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Award No. 106 L-E S.D. 1374, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Award No. 41 LE - S.D., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- TE - 17745, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- TE-18251 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- TE - 18250, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Award NO. 88 L-E, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Award No. 89 LE, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Award No. 90 -LE, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Award No. 91-LE, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Award No. 92 LE, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Award No. 93-LE, 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Award NO. 94 L-E, 1938-1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Award No. 12 LE, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Award No. 13 LE, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Award No. 14 -LE, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Award No. 15 - LE, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Award No. 16 -LE, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Award No. 17, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Award NO. 18 -LE, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Award No. 19, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Award NO. 20 -LE, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Award No. 21 -LE, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Award No. 6 Case No. 6, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Awards, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- SBA #718, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- SBA #718 Case No. 742-188, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- SBA #718 Case No. 742-205 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- SBA #718 Case No. 742-210, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- SBA #718 Case No. 957-262, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- SBA #718 Case No. 957-263, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- SBA# 718 Case No. 871-111, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- SBA #718 Case No. 877-120, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- SBA #718 Case No. 817-723, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- SBA #718 Case NO. 871-125, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- SBA #715 Case No. 817-126, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- SBA #718 - Case No. 871-132, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- SBA # 718 Case No. 871-142, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- SBA #718 Case No. 871-145, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- SBA #718 Case No. 871-153, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- SBA #718 Case No. 871-155, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- SBA #718 Case No. 871-156, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- SBA #718 Case No. 957-267 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- SBA # 724, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- SBA #724 Award No. 22 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- SBA #724 Award No. 23 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Award No. 2 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Award No. 4 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Award No. 5 SBA#729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Award No. 6 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Award No. 7 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Award No. 8 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Award No. 9 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Award No.10 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Award No. 11 SBA #729, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Award No. 12 SBA #729 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Award No. 13 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Award NO. 14 SBA #729, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Award No. 15 SBA #729, 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- SBA #724 Award No. 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- SBA #724 Award No. 2, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- SBA #724 Award No. 3, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- SBA #724 Award No. 4 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- SBA #724 Award No. 9, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- SBA #724 Award No. 10, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- SBA #724 Award No. 11, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- SBA #724 Award No. 12, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- SBA #724 Award No. 13, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- SBA #724 Award No. 15, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- SBA #724 Award No. 16, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- SBA #724 Award No. 17, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- SBA #724 Award No. 18, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- SBA #724 Award No. 19, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- SBA #724 Award No. 20, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- SBA #724 Award No. 6, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- SBA #724 Award No. 7, 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- SBA #724 Award No. 14, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- SBA #724 Award No. 24, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- SBA #724 Award No. 25, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- SBA #724 Award No. 26, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- SBA #724 Award No. 27 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- SBA #724 Award No. 28, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- SBA #724 Award No. 29, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- SBA #724 Award No. 30, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- SBA #724 Award No. 31, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- SBA #724 Award No. 32, 1932-1965 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Awards -PL #468 New Haven -BLE, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Award No. 29 -S.D., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Award No. 30 S.D., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Award No. 31 -LE, 1964-1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Award No. 32 S.D., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Award No. 33-L-E S.D. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Award No. 35-E S.D. E-1232, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Award 36-LE- S.D. 1234, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Award No. 37-LE- S.D., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Award No. 38 LE S.D., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Award No. 39 - S.D., 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Award No. 40 -L-E, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Special Board of Adjustment, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Award No. 43 -L-E, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Award No. 44-L-E, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Award No. 45-L-E, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Award No. 46-L-E, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Awards, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Public Law Board No. 543, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Several More Awards, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Shop Crafts Special Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Shop Crafts Special Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Shop Crafts Special Board of Adjustment, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Case 73, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Case No. 32, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Case #74, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Award No. 7-L-W, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Award No. 53-L-W, 1956-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Award No. 54-L-W, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Award No. 55-L-W, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Award No. 68-L-W, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- P.L. Board No. 326, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Award No. 49-L-W, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Award No. 50-L-W, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Award No. 51-L-W, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Award No. 52-L-W, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Award No. 45-L-W, 1956-1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- P.L. Board No. 326, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Award No. 39-L-W, 1954-1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- P.L. Board No. 326, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Award No. 41-L-W, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- P.L. 326 - Award No. 42-L-W, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Award No. 43-L-W, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 29-L-W, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- P.L. #326 Award No. 28-L-W, 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- P.L. 326 Award No. 30-L-W, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Award No. 31-L-W P.L. Board 326, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Award No. 32-L-W, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- P.L. Board 326 Award No. 33-LW, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 34-LW, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Award No. 35-L-W P.L. Board No. 326, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 36-LW, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Award No. 37-L-W, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Award No. 38-L-W P.L. Board 1283, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Award No. 27-L-W, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Award No. 1-L-W, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Award No. 6-LW, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Award No. 8-L-W, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Award No. 9-L-W, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Award No. 10-L-W, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Award No. 11-L-W, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Award No. 116-L-W, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Award No. 13-L-W P.L. Board 326, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Award 14-L-W P.L. 326, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- P.L. Board #326 Award No. 16-L-W, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 17-L-W, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 15-L-W, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Award No. 19 P.L. #326, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Award No. 20-L-W, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Award no. 22-L-W, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Award No. 23-L-W P.L. 326, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Award No. 21-L-W P.L. 326 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Award No. 25-L-W, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Special Board of Adjustment, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Carrier's Statement of Facts, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 26-LW, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 27-LW, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- P.L. Board No. 326 Award No. 18-LE, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Award No. 6-LE, 1958-1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Award No. 2-L-W, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Award No. 3-L-W, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Award No. 4-L-W, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Arbitration, 1958-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1 Photograph
- Award No. 1-L-E, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2-L-E, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Award NO. 4-LE, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Award No. 24-LE P.L. 326 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Operating Employees' Vacation Agreement, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Vacation Agreement, 1945-1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Award No. 9 P.L. 413, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Award No. 10 - P.L 413, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Award No. 11 - P.L. 413, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Award No. 12 P.L. 413, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Award No. 13 - P.L. 413, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- National Vacation Agreement, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Vacation Agreement BLF&E, 1949-1963 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- National Vacation Agreement, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- National Vacation Agreement BRT-W-65, 1949-1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- National Vacation Agreement BLE-29-W, 1949-1963 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- CL-16148, 1948-1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- CL-16344, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- CL-16510, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Award No. 1- (CL-16148), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2 (CL-16344), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Award NO. 3 P.L. #3 (CL-16510), 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- National Vacation Agreement, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- National Vacation Agreement BRT-64-E, 1949-1956 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- National Vacation Agreement, 1949-1963 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- National Vacation Agreement BRT-W-58, 1949-1960 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- National Vacation Agreement BRT-W-63, 1949-1963 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- National Vacation Agreement BRT-W-64, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- National Vacation Agreement, 1949-1956 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- P.L. Board No. 11 Award No. 1, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- P.L. Board No. 11 Award No. 2, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- SBA #679 Yard Claim #1, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- SBA# 679 - Road Claim #2, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- SBA #679-Road Claim No. 3, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- SBA# 679 - Road Claim #4, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- PBA# 679 - Road Claim #5, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- PBA# 679 - Road Claim #6, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- PBA# 619 - Award 7-8 -Road, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- PBA# 679 - Road Claim #9, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- SBA# 679 - Road Claim No. 10, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- SBA#679 - Road Claim No. 11, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- SBA #679 Land Claim #1 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- SBA #679 -Land Claim No. 2, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- SBA #679 Land Claim #3, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- SBA #679 - Land No. 4, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Award No. 2 - P.L. #413, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Award No. 3 -P.L. #413, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Award No. 4 - P.L. #413, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Award No. 5 - P.L. #413, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Award No. 6 - P.L. #413, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Award No. 7 P.L. #413, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Award No. 8 P.L. #413, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- P.L. No. 969 Award No. 1676, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Public Law Board No. 969, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Award No. 1680+1683, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Award No. 4, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Award No. 1682 - P.L. Bd. 969, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Award No. 1688 P.L. Board No. 969, 1963-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Award No.1689 P.L. Board 969, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Award No. 1690 P.L. Board 969, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Award No. 1691 P.L. Board 969, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- P.L. 969 Award No. 1692, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Awards No. 1695, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Public Law board No. 217, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Public Law Board No. 217, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2-E-2 SBA #258, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Award No. 3 - Case 3-E, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Award No. 4 - E-4, 1958-1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Award 5-7 SBA #258, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Award No. 6 Withdrawn, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Award No. 8 - Case 5-8 SBA# 258, 1958-1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Award No. 9 E-9 SBA #258, 1958-1970 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Award No. 1511, 1961-1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Award No. 12 -E-12 SBA #258, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Award No. 13 -E-13 SBA #258, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Award No. 14 -E-14 SBA #258, 1958-1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Award No. 15 -E-15 SBA #258, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Award No. 16 E-16, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Award No. 17, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Award No. 18 -E-18 SBA #258, 1958-1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Award No. 19, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Award No. 20 E-20, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Award No. 7 SBA #625, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Award No. 4 SBA #625, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Award No. 1 SBA #625, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Award No. 2 SBA #625, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Award No. 3 SBA #625, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Award No. 5 SBA #625, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Award No. 6 SBA #625, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Award No. 10 SBA #625, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Award No. 8 SBA #625, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Award No. 9 SBA #625, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Award No. 11 SBA #625, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Award No. 12 - SBA #625, 1965-1969 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Award No. 13 SBA #625, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- P.L. Board No. 467 - Award No. 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Award No. 326 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Award No. 3-L-E; E-1252 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Award No. 9-L-W; E.D. 105 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Award No. 5 - LW; E.D. 27 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Award No. 11 - L-E; S.D. - E.D. - 103 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Award No. 8 - L.E. - S.D. - E.D. - 84 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Award No. 10 - Lines East - SD - ED - 97 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Award No. 9 - Lines East - SD-ED - 87 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Award No. 10 - L-W - E.D. - 107 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Award No. 11 - Lines West - S.D. - E.D. - 109 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- NFW - 139 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- P.L. Board No. 467 - Award No. 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- SBA #455 Cases 4,5,7,6 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Award No. 2 - P.L. Board No. 467 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Award No. 3 - P.L. No. 467 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Award No. 4-P.L. Board No. 467 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Award No. 5 P.L. Board #474 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Award No. 1 P.L. #498 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Mr. Seidenberg SUNA (Special Board No. 459 / Item No. 11) (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Mr. Seidenberg SUNA Special Board No. 459/Item No. 12 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Mr. Seidenberg SUNA Special Board No. 459 Item No. 13 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Mr. Seidenberg SUNA Special Board No. 459 Item No. 14 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (Box 8, Folder 24)
- SBAs (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Award No. 12 - Lines West - S.D. - E.D. - 116 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Exhibit #1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Award No. 4: P.L. Board No. 474 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 455 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Hostler Cases: Rearguard (Box 9, Folder 4)